<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Document>
	<Columns>
		<Column>
			<Name>Root</Name>
			<Value>0</Value>
		</Column>
		<Column>
			<Name>Level1</Name>
			<Value>2</Value>
		</Column>
		<Column>
			<Name>Level2</Name>
			<Value>6</Value>
		</Column>
		<Column>
			<Name>Description</Name>
			<Value>25</Value>
		</Column>
	</Columns>
	<Data>
		<Text Column="Root">Stream Visualizer is an application that can be used to visualize, capture and replay data streams.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Root">Parameters:</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">&lt;port&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Specifies that all streams of &lt;port&gt; should be included in the stream selection list. A test packet will be retrieved from the specified port to build a list of possible streams before the visualization begins.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">&lt;port&gt;:&lt;streams&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Specifies that the &lt;streams&gt; of &lt;port&gt; should be included in the stream selection list.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">&lt;streams&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">&lt;range&gt;,&lt;range&gt;,...</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">&lt;range&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">&lt;path&gt;[=&lt;name&gt;]|&lt;path&gt;-&lt;path&gt;</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">&lt;path&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">A path to the stream, subpaths are seperated by dots. For example "1.2.3" specifies that the stream should be generated from the third value in the second list in the first list of the port.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">+m|-m</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Enables or disables minimal mode. In minimal mode, everything except for the graph area is hidden from the user interface to maximize the available drawing-space. The default value is disabled.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">+e|-e</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Enables or disables the graph extension feature. When graph extension is enabled, all graphs that have at least one sampled data entry are extended across the whole width of the coordinate system using known adjacent values. The default value is enabled.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">+a|-a</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Enables or disables antialiasing of graph lines. The default value is enabled.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">+b|-b</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Enables or disables alpha-blending. The default value is enabled.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">+v|-v</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Enables or disables vertical synchronization. The default value is enabled.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">+c|-c</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Enables or disables the regular clearing of old received data. Enable if you plan to run the visualizer for a long time and you don't want to save the results. The default value is disabled.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">t:(c|s[:&lt;c&gt;]|w[:&lt;c&gt;])</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Lets you specify the type of time manager that is used. The default value is "c".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">c</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Continuous time manager. The graphs are drawn across the entire drawing-area, the most recent data entry lies on the right border of the drawing-area.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">s[:&lt;c&gt;]</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Shifting time manager. The graphs will shift &lt;c&gt; times the drawing-area width to the left whenever the most recent data entry reaches the right border of the drawing-area. The default value for &lt;c&gt; is "0.8".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">w[:&lt;c&gt;]</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Wrapping time manager. The graphs don't move at all, once the most recent data entry reaches the right border, the graphs wrap around and draw over the oldest entries starting from the left. The most recent data entry will push a gap of &lt;c&gt; times the drawing-area width in front of it. The default value for &lt;c&gt; is "0.2".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">w:&lt;width&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Lets you specify the width of the drawing-area in total seconds. The default value is "10".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />		
		<Text Column="Level1">v:(d|s[:&lt;low&gt;:&lt;high&gt;]</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Lets you specify the type of value manager that is used. The default value is "d".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">d</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Fitting (dynamic) value manager. The Y-Axis will be automatically scaled to fit all the values that are currently visualized.</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">s[:&lt;low&gt;:&lt;high&gt;]</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Fixed (static) value manager. You can manually specify the range of values along the Y-Axis. The default value for &lt;low&gt;:&lt;high&gt; is "0:1".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />		
		<Text Column="Level1">s:(s[:&lt;c&gt;]|p[:&lt;c&gt;])</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Lets you specify the data manager type and settings used for drawing graphs. The default value is "p:1".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">s[:&lt;c&gt;]</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Per-Second data manager. The data will be resampled to &lt;c&gt; entries per second. The default value for &lt;c&gt; is "10".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level2">p[:&lt;c&gt;]</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Per-Pixel data manager. The data will be resampled to &lt;c&gt; entries per pixel. The default value for &lt;c&gt; is "0.1".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">l:&lt;width&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Lets you specify the width (thickness) of the graph lines in pixels. The default value is "1.0".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">mx:&lt;n&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Sets the number of markers that are displayed on the X-Axis. The default value is "5".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">my:&lt;n&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Sets the number of markers that are displayed on the Y-Axis. The default value is "5".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">pc:&lt;color&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Sets the diagram color (coordinate system and labels) in HTML notation. The default value is "FFFFFF".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
		<Text Column="Level1">bc:&lt;color&gt;</Text>
		<Text Column="Description">Sets the background color in HTML notation. The default value is "000000".</Text>
		<NewLine />
		<NewLine />
	</Data>
</Document>